NO BOY NO CRY ore zenshin GO
no boy, no cry, I advance go!
shounen yo kiite kure
hey boys, listen up
ningen nante taishita mon ja nai sa
humans aren't such a big deal
ashita nante moui ranai kara
who needs tomorrow anyway
nigitta kobushi wo kakusu na yo
so don't hide your fists
fuan ni yume wo
you're not old enough
uri tobasu hodo mada oiborechainai daro
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
shounen yo kokoro no jyuu no
hey boys, you're the only ones
hikigane wo hikeru no wa kimi dake sa
who can pull the trigger in your heart
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
doushi yo mo naku kudaranai
we're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
kono subarashii sekai ni tattaima ikiteiru kara
awesome world right at this moment,
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
subete no hontou to uso wo
don't forget every truth or lie
kesshite wasurete shima wa nai you ni
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
shinu ni wa mosugiru darou
we're way too young to die
shiraketa tsura ga naranderu karappo no kono machi de
in this empty town lined with empty faces
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids took off
kaze no nai kono yoru ni
into this windless night
nanika wo kaeyou to shiteru kara
because they want to change something
{The Strict Guards
{of the Facility
{The Three Bad Boys
All right!
I can start my training!
Right now this is all I can do.
I can't allow myself to fail!
What's up?
Going to all the trouble of coming
to pick me up like this...
You're on your way to Kurenai-sensei's
after this anyway, right...?
Taking the time to converse
once in a while...
that's also part of teamwork.
Let me hear about your mission.
It was pretty incredible...
But you wouldn't understand
even if I explained it to you.
I don't want Akamaru to experience
that kind of thing ever again.
And for that reason I must polish
my Jutsu all the more...
I want to hear about it in detail.
Because that's what teamwork
is about.
Are you sulking
'cause you were the only one
who was passed up?
You are sulking aren't you?
There have to be more further up...
Until I can see it...
I can't believe you're doing
that from the morning...
Neji, let's take a break.
Okay!
— Let's go, Hinata!
— Okay!
Father, see you later.
Barbecued meat?
This early in the morning, huh?
Just when he was looking good
after losing some weight
when he was released
from the hospital.
He made an amazing rebound
didn't he?
With that good an appetite
there aren't any more worries
about his health are there?
When I'm done eating
help me with my training, okay?
Asuma-sensei!
Hey, are you an idiot
or something?!
You're recuperating you know!
L-Lee... Come on
let's take a short break...
What's the matter, Guy-sensei?
The prime of one's youth waits
for no one you know.
Maintaining the prime of one's youth
is starting to get tough...
Thank you very much!
Do your best guys...
I'll master the Shuriken Jutsu by
the next time you're here!
M-Me too...
I want to become a Kunoichi
just like you Temari-san...
I'm honoured.
I apologize for asking you
to teach at the Academy...
since we're so short-staffed right now.
You probably would've preferred
to go sightseeing or something.
No problem.
I'm doing this because I enjoy it.
Yeah... And we were also able to survey
the future potential of
the Leaf's military power...
Well be careful going home.
Okay...
If something happens again
I'll come to your rescue again.
Just let me know, crybaby.
You always say too much.
That's why girls are...
Let's kick butt again today, Akamaru!
All right everybody's here, right?
You don't need to be so tense, Hinata...
Y-Yeah...
All right! Everybody stand ready!
I can't... lose to Naruto-kun...!
All right! I'm ready!
I just have to wait
for Pervy Sage to come...!
There he is!
But my training...
Don't get so pouty, Naruto.
Some work came in all of a sudden.
It can't be helped.
It's just gonna be doing
an interview
for some obscene magazine
anyway, right?
That kind of thing isn't called work.
It's a mission to gather information
about the Akatsuki Organization.
But if I tell this guy that
he might ask me to
let him come.
Humph!
I'll make it up to you by...
Huh?
W-What's this?
It's so that you don't get bored
while you're staying at home
it's a special training menu
I put together!
Wow!
Wait, wait!
My own prized secret training
methods are inscribed here.
Don't read this where
other people might see it!
Okay!
Well, do your best!
I'm gonna use this
to train vigorously!
Thank you, Pervy Sage!
The walls have ears...
paper doors have eyes...
Pervy Sage's secret training methods...
{"WILLPOWER"
What?!
Pervy Sage!
Since I have been entrusted
with the great Village Hidden
in the Leaves that you built
no matter what danger might strike
it is my duty to protect it.
The Hokage sure has it tough, huh.
Yes, you really do.
Is that you, Shizune?
Enter!
All of these reports regarding
the village's internal affairs accumulated
because so many things
were happening in the Leaf Village.
I guess the only thing to do
is start at the top.
Leaf Maximum Security Facility.
Did its name change?
Yes, in the past
it was called
Prison Specializing in
Capital Offenses Ninja.
Fortunately, because there
is a downward trend
in felonies committed by Shinobi
along with the downsizing of the facility
the name was changed as well.
Incarcerated are murderers,
those who were involved in
leaking classified secrets and so on.
They are all criminal Ninja...
There haven't been any noticeable
disruptions in the past few years
and the facility has been
relatively stable.
— Food!
It's finally time to eat
isn't it, an-chan!
Yeah! I'm so excited!
Hey! Fujin! Raijin!
If you don't shut up
you're gonna go without dinner!
Gimme a break! Those guys...
You may pass!
Hey! Wait!
You're hurt, aren't you?
Go to the dispensary later
and have that looked at.
Okay...
All right next!
H-Hey, an-chan...
Huh?
Why is the little finger
short and weak?
That's easy, Raijin.
If the little finger was thick and strong
then your thumb would
have no leg to stand on.
I-I see!
An-chan... An-chan...!
— Huh?
— A lizard!
Raijin, you've always been
a dandy one from way back.
W-We haven't had enough to eat
have we, an-chan?
Yeah...
Not asking permission again...
What's the matter?
What's up this time?
I'm starving...
G-Give us something to eat!
Oh no... If these guys find out
I don't have anything...!
Um... right now...
Don't tell me that
you don't have even one offering...
to these Fujin and
Raijin brothers?!
Well... wait... wait...!
What do you think? Tastes good, huh?
I'll bring you something else later!
Right now, make do with that!
— Okay!
Are you okay?
Those guys are quiet
when they have food.
But if they get angry
they're out of control.
Yeah... They annihilated all their comrades
over food during a mission
and the people around just barely
managed to hold them down.
Something smells good?!
Yeah.
This way!
— Food! Food! Food!
I just can't get to liking clerical work.
There's still a whole lot more to do,
Tsunade-sama.
I wonder what this is?
It looks like a formula
for some kind of medicine...
A formula...
Send an available Jonin here
immediately!
Yes ma'am?
Hurry!
Y-Yes ma'am!
How about it...
Does it taste good?
I see... I see...
There's still a whole lot more.
Just as I thought
that good smell was coming
from your place, aniki!
Uh yeah...'Cause aniki
always has delicious food!
It was worth sneaking, wasn't it?
'Cause I'd feel so sorry
if you guys had to go hungry.
Aniki...
— A lizard!
I see, I see... Happy?
How about it, you guys?
Don't you want to eat things
that are even more delicious?
W-Where are they at?!
If we go to the place where
an old friend of mine is...
you can pig out on food
that's even more delicious than here.
Is that the guy you told us
about long time ago, aniki?
Yeah, Orochimaru-sama...
Gimme a break...
that guy's gotta be kidding!
That Pervy Sage...
just leaving me and
my training up in the air!
Come on don't say that, Naruto.
Jiraiya-sama had a mission too.
Heh!
It's probably that
Tsunade-sama decided
that only Jiraiya-sama
could do the job...
It can't be helped.
Damn! So it was Grandma Tsunade's
doing after all, huh!
Well, I guess all I can do is treat you
to some ramen noodles like this.
So cheer up.
I'm gonna go complain
to Grandma Tsunade!
Thanks for the meal, Iruka-sensei!
N-Naruto!
Damn... another annoying situation.
Huh? The Maximum Security Facility?!
This is about a year ago
a Chunin Academy staff member
used Naruto
to sneak out
the Scroll of Sealing.
According to the report it was
a crime committed by Mizuki acting alone.
The crime was solved but...?
Yeah, if it really was him acting alone.
The possibility has arisen that
a bigger mastermind is behind this crime.
This is a clue...
This is something that Mizuki
was concealing
when he was incarcerated
in the Maximum Security Facility.
At the time nobody thought of it
as anything more than a doodle.
Tsunade-sama, what is that anyway?
I don't know, however...
The handwriting resembles
the document confiscated from the facility
where Orochimaru was conducting
human experiments...
Which means that...
Orochimaru is connected to this crime?!
The possibility of that is not zero.
It's not like a Chunin alone could do
anything with the Scroll of Sealing.
It would only make sense if Orochimaru
were pulling strings from behind.
Asuma! Kurenai!
Go immediately to the Maximum
Security Facility and interrogate Mizuki!
Orochimaru?!
Be careful! Something's strange here!
Yeah... It's too quiet.
Let's go!
Oh, how touching.
A welcome party for us...
Yeah... we're giving you a big welcome.
Right, an-chan?
Yeah...
Asuma, don't tell me that
those guys are...
Uh huh... The legendary idiot brothers...
Fujin and Raijin!
Asuma...
Hey, you guys are whooping it up
too much for a welcome party!
Hey, calm down...
the welcome party's just started.
His character has changed completely...
All you jerks...
You will... be our offering!
Do it!
Orochimaru!
Asuma-sensei... Kurenai-sensei!
kusottare na nyuusu ga toori sugite
crappy news pass us by
kimi wa kotoba wo nakusu
and you become speechless
boku no koe ja marude chiisa sugite
my voice is way too soft
kimi wa henji mo shinai
so you don't answer
kimi ga naiteru hitori de naiteru
you're crying, crying alone
boku wa dou suru boku mo naiteru no sa
what can I do? I'm crying too
yoru ni hitoribocchi no ore no sakebi ni nosete
"let my lonely scream ring out through the night"
zawameku jidai wo ore no supiido de buttobashiteku yeah yeah yeah yeah
I'll thrash this confused era with my speed, yeah
sanzameku yoru mo ore no supiido de buttobashiteku yeah yeah yeah yeah
and I'll thrash this confused night with my speed, yeah
tsunzaku gitaa to ore no supiido de buttobashiteku yeah yeah yeah yeah
I'll thrash them with my piercing guitar and my speed, yeah
katamuku sekai mo warui yatsura mo kechirashiteku yeah yeah yeah yeah
I'll take this sinking world, all its evil bastards, and kick their butts, yeah
What's the matter Tonton?
What in the world happened?
Say, weren't you together
with Shizune nee-chan?
Don't tell me something's
happened to her?
I don't know what happened
but take me there, Tonton!
I'm getting a bad feeling about this!
Next time:
"Run, Tonton! We're on your nose."